Toni Morrison Papers, 1957-: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Writings, 1929 September-2015; 100 boxes (3 partial)
  - Subseries 1: Novels, 1929 September-2015; 66 boxes (4 partial)
    - Love, 2000-2003; 7 boxes
      - Chapter 6, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 6, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 6, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - L5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - L2, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - "The hiking boots...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - "Heed can't look...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - "The hiking boots...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - "Heed eased down...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - "An orange-scented road...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - "The hiking boots...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - "Heed can't look...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - "I see you...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - "You are always thinking about death...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - "I see you...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - "The women's legs are spread wide open...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - "Vida set up the ironing board...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - "The Ocean is my man now...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - "Correctional girls knew better...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Various Corrected Pages, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - "...the door and asked her if she could take Romen on as after school help.", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
        Pages 5-11.
      - "[They begin to talk]", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
        Pages 3-15.
      - "Uneasy with other men's sexual confidences...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
        Pages 6-18.
      - "...dollar bill, May said...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
        Pages 6-10.
      - "She never took her eyes off the trays...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
        Pages 7-19.
      - "...no one to stop him...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
        Pages 12-15.
      - "Junior, huddled over her knees...", undated; 1 item
        Pages 309-310.
      - "Junior, huddled over her knees...", undated; 1 item
      - "Sandler admitted he could have imagined the look...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - "Correctional girls knew better...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - "The hiking boots...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - "Heed can't look...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - "I see you...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - "I don't know what to say to the boy...", portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 1, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 1, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
        Pages 1-47.
      - Chapter 1, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
        Pages 15-47.
      - Chapter 2, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 2, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 4, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - L2, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - L2, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 4, June 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - L3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - L, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 5: Lover, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 6: Bachelor, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 6, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 6: Husband, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - L4, June 3; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 9: Phantom, June 6; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - L5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - L5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - L, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - L, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 10, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 9, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - L3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 9, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - L4, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Chapter Titles, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - L: b, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
        Pages 47-52.
      - End of Chapter 8, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 10: Phantom, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - "Sometimes children fall in love...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 3, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - "Vida was all he knew...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
        1 p. (page 22 of 30).
      - Chapter 8: Father, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - "You are always thinking about death...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - "I don't know what to say to the boy...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Draft, 2002 June-September; 1 item Printout. (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Draft, 2002 October 1; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
      - Draft, 2003 January 29; 1 item Printout. (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
        With Robert Gottlieb's annotations.
      - Draft, undated; 1 item (Box 44, Folder 6-7)
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
        Pages 1-319.
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders (Box 45, Folder 3-4)
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders (Box 45, Folder 5-6)
      - Rough Page Proofs, 2003 April 29; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Rough Page Proofs Author's Set, 2003 April 23; 1 item (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Revised Page Proofs #1, 2003 June 24; 1 item (Box 46, Folder 3-4)
      - Essence Excerpt, 2003 July 18; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Third Pass Pages, 2003 August 20; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Revised Page Proofs #2 Master Set, 2003 August 22; 1 item (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Advance Copy, 2003; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Design/Production, 2003; 2 folders (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
    - A Mercy, 2006-2009; 8 boxes
      As "Notes for Proposal" indicates, A Mercy was originally conceived of as a 3-part novel, later becoming a trilogy including Home and God Help the Child; early outlines and drafts thus include material relating to all three novels.
      - Research Material, 6 folders (Box 48, Folder 1-6, Box 49, Folder 1-5)
      - Notes for Proposal, undated; 1 item (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Outlines and Notes, undated; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Chronology/Outline: Mercy 3/Florens, undated; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - "He moved carefully through the water...", undated; 1 folder Notepad pages. (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - "Now in an abyss...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - "The man moved carefully...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - "To purposefully throw oneself...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - "Trust me.", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - "...leather.", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - "Lila", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - "Don't be afraid...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - "I stop by a rock...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - "Dear S.", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - "inserts Rebekka", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - "Add:", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - "1. Florens 1st per.", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - "Examining her body", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Mercy One, undated; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Mercy Two, undated; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Mercy Three, undated; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Manuscripts 2006 [Early Drafts], 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - Draft, 2006; 1 item Printout, corrected.
        - Draft, 2006; 1 item Printout, corrected.
        - Draft, 2006; 1 item Printout, corrected.
        - Draft, 2006; 1 item Printout, corrected.
        - Draft, 2006; 1 item Printout, corrected.
        - Draft, 2006; 1 item Printout, corrected.
          Toni Morrison has required the Library to make surrogate copies of all of her manuscripts (including typescripts and proofs) and diaries (appointment books), including but not restricted to those damaged by fire in 1993. This is for conservation reasons, to prevent damage and deterioration by repeated use. Researchers are required to use digital surrogates in the reading room of the Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.s.
        - Draft, 2006; 1 item Printout, corrected.
        - Draft, 2006; 1 item Printout, corrected.
          Pages 1-32.
        - Draft, 2006; 1 item Printout, corrected.
      - Florens [Early Drafts], 5 folders (4 partial)
        - Draft, June 26; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-38.
        - Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 3)
          Pages 21-24.
        - Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - Draft, July 9; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-44.
        - Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 6)
          Pages 41-42.
      - Draft, 2006 December 10; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Draft, 2006 December 13; portion of 1 folder Printout. (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 5)
        Pages 23-26.
      - Draft, undated; portion of 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 6)
        Pages 1-50.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 7)
        Pages 1-52.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 8)
        Pages 1-56.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 9)
        Pages 1-60.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 10)
        Pages 7-64.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 11)
        Pages 20-70.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 51, Folder 12)
        Pages 7-75.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 1)
        Pages 1-83.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 2)
        Pages 1-90.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 3)
        Pages 1-91.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 4)
        Pages 7-96.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 5)
        Pages 33-63.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 6)
        Pages 82-104 (pencil 112).
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 7)
        Pages 1-115.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 8)
        Pages 1-123.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 1)
        Pages 42-174.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 3)
        Pages 1-40.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 4)
        Pages 81-119.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 5)
        Pages 1-192.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 6)
        Pages 1-197.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 9)
        Pages 151-166.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 10)
        Pages 183-199.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 11)
        Pages 179-199.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 12)
        Various revised pages.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 13)
        Pages 1-207.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 14)
        Pages 65-89.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 15)
        Pages 214-220.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 16)
        Pages 192-219.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 17)
        Revised pages, unnumbered.
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders Printout, corrected. (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
        Pages 1-227.
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders Printout, corrected. (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
        Pages 1-234.
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders Printout, corrected. (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
        Pages 1-237.
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders Printout, corrected (photocopy). (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
        Pages 1-241.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 54, Folder 9)
        Pages 190-233.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Draft, 2008; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
        Pages 1-241. With Robert Gottlieb's annotations and correspondence from Robert Gottlieb's assistant Sarah Rothbard, dated January 15, 2008.
      - Draft, 2008; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 55, Folder 3-4)
        Pages 1-241. With Robert Gottlieb's edits transferred in red pencil.
      - Draft, circa 2008; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 55, Folder 5)
        Revised pages.
      - Bound Manuscript, 2008; 1 item Printout. (Box 55, Folder 6)
        Pages 1-241. With note from Sarah Rothbard at Knopf, dated February 8, 2008.
      - Setting Copy, 2008; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 55, Folder 7-8)
      - Author's Set First Pass Rough Pages, 2008 March 21; 1 item (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - First Pass Page Proofs, 2008 March 21; 1 item (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Author's Set Second Pass Page Proofs, 2008 May 15; 1 item (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Advance Copy, 2008; 1 item (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Design/Production, 2008-2009; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Home, 2008-2012; 6 boxes
      Working title Frank Money.
      - Research Files, 2 boxes
        - 1950s, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - The American City H 20 1948, 1957, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - Atlanta Tram/Bus, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 3)
        - Georgia Department of Public Health Report 1951, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - Georgia H 20, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 5)
        - Georgia Legislature Role in H 20 Supply, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 6)
        - The Green Book, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 7)
        - Greyhound Bus Routes: Seattle-Chicago-Atlanta, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 8)
        - High Cotton, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 9)
        - Korea, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 10)
        - Life Magazine, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 11)
        - Military Pay & Benefits, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 12)
        - Miscellaneous, undated; 4 folders (Box 58, Folder 1-4, Box 57, Folder 13-14)
        - Miscellaneous Atlanta Constitution April 1952, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 5)
        - Quilts, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 6)
        - Rents: Atlanta April 1952, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 7)
        - Restaurants of Seattle 1853-1960, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 8)
        - Sanitary City, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 9)
        - Seattle Central District Housing, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 10)
        - Southeast Drainage Basins, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 11)
        - Trains: Chicago-Atlanta, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 12)
        - Trains: Portland-Chicago, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 13)
        - Wages: Atlanta April 1952, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 14)
        - Weather: Atlanta April 1952, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Proposal and Outlines, circa 2008-2011; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - "Cee/rescue", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - "On the bees", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - "p. 25 Decent women delivered babies at home...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - "Frank's return home", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - "Cee sitting in Ethel's backyard gardens", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - "The eruptions (s. shock incidents)", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - "I can tell now...", undated; 1 folder Notepad. (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - "Memoire", undated; 1 folder Notepad pages. (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Nothings II [Outline and Early Draft], undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Frank Money and Bride [Outline and Early Draft], undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Draft, July 29; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Draft, September 5; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 19)
        Pages 28-29.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 20)
        Pages 26-28.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 59, Folder 21)
        Pages 20-32.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 26)
        Pages 1-51.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 59, Folder 27)
      - Draft, June 15; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 59, Folder 28)
        Pages 1-65.
      - Draft, July 1; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 1)
        Pages 1-71.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 2)
        Pages 1-68.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 3)
        Pages 63-74.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 4)
        Pages 59-77.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 5)
        Pages 5-97.
      - Draft, January 22; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 6)
        Pages 1-96.
      - Draft, March 20; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 7)
        Pages 1-105.
      - Draft, May 16; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 8)
        Pages 1-120.
      - Draft, May 29; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 9)
        Pages 1-128.
      - Draft, June 1; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 60, Folder 10)
        Pages 1-137.
      - Draft, June 13; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 61, Folder 1)
        Pages 1-149.
      - Draft, July 3; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 61, Folder 2)
        Pages 1-172.
      - Draft, July 7; 1 folder Printout. (Box 61, Folder 3)
        Pages 1-135.
      - Draft, July 17; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 61, Folder 4)
        Pages 1-181.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout. (Box 61, Folder 5)
        Pages 1-194.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 61, Folder 6)
        Pages 1-198.
      - Copyedited Manuscript, 2011 October 27; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Copyedited Manuscript with Robert Gottlieb and Toni Morrison edits, 2011 November 14; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Setting Copy, 2011; 1 item Printout, corrected. (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Page Proofs, 2011 December 7; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Corrected Proof Pages, 2011 December 7; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Page Proofs, 2012 February 16; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Laser Proofs, 2012; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 7-8)
      - Layout Samples, 2011; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Advance Copy, 2012; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Dust-jacket Sample, 2012; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - God Help the Child, 2012 December 21-2015; 4 boxes
      Working titles Bride, Bride Anew, Goodness, and The Wrath of Children.
      - Research Files, 3 files
        - Make-Up, undated; 1 file (Box 63, File 1)
        - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - Prison, undated; 1 file (Box 63, File 3)
      - Outlines and Notes, undated; 1 folder Notepad pages and printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - "Man: I met a woman...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 64, Folder 2)
        Includes material relating to A Mercy and Home.
      - "Bride 1. Direction of her journey...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - "Wrath of Children", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - "1. Queen", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - "Orchestration", undated; 1 folder Notepad pages and printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Draft, 2006 March 26, revised 2011 July 29; 1 folder Printout. (Box 64, Folder 9)
        Page 1-40.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 10)
        Pages 57-66.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 11)
        Pages 1-70.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 12)
        Pages 1-81.
      - Draft, 2012 December 21; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 14)
        Pages 1-63.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 15)
        Pages 78-86.
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 16)
        Pages 78-96.
      - Draft, December 23; 1 folder Printout, corrected. (Box 64, Folder 17)
        Pages 1-78.
      - Draft, December 23; 1 folder Printout. (Box 64, Folder 18)
        Insert.